<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>   on smaller infinity</title>
    <link>https://smallerinfinity.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in    on smaller infinity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 06:57:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://smallerinfinity.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maggie Dream</title>
      <link>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/maggie-dream-wagner-mall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 06:33:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/maggie-dream-wagner-mall/</guid>
      <description>Last night, I dreamt of Maggie.
It was the regular disjointed dream, mostly. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember lots of it. But in the end, I was at the Wagner Mall in Bend, but like it was when I was a kid. I was in a store that I think I owned, and my Mom was there and the kids. Maggie came in and was talking and piddling around doing stuff, but it was a sidebar to what was going on in the dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#NoEstimates and Story Sizing</title>
      <link>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/noestimates-and-story-sizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 04:28:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/noestimates-and-story-sizing/</guid>
      <description>In my last post about #noestimates, I touched briefly on story sizing. This prompted a couple of questions from a thoughtful reviewer.
  What made you pick 5 days as the right size? Are you just comparing the stories to previous ones to say - yep, this feels like 5 days compared to the last x number of stories that we have sized in the past?   Let&amp;rsquo;s dig into this some more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Approach to #NoEstimates</title>
      <link>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/my-approach-to-noestimates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 09:02:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/my-approach-to-noestimates/</guid>
      <description>For the two and a half years, I&amp;rsquo;ve been running projects with significantly less estimation ceremony. The approach has not been perfect, nor has it been entirely without estimation of any kind. Here&amp;rsquo;s an overview on how I tried to make it work.
Backlog Setup At the beginning of each project, I met with Product Owners repeatedly, for deep dive conversations about what they wanted out of the project. My starting goal was to identify the least amount of work possible to barely satisfy the project needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Day at BIOVIA</title>
      <link>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/final-day-at-biovia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 06:44:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/final-day-at-biovia/</guid>
      <description>Today is my last day at BIOVIA. It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly twelve years. I&amp;rsquo;m excited and afraid, prepared and uncertain, glad for something new and grateful for everything customary.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been really lucky here. I&amp;rsquo;ve had some great mentors and trainers. I&amp;rsquo;ve received the wonderful gift of leaders giving me opportunities and getting out of my way to work on them. I&amp;rsquo;ve travelled to cool places. I&amp;rsquo;ve made friends in far flung corners of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sula&#39;s Final Moments</title>
      <link>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/sula-final-moments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 08:03:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/sula-final-moments/</guid>
      <description>Sula died Friday, 15 June 2018. She was ten years old.
We had planned a family camping trip for the weekend, at a nice site at the headwaters of the Deschutes River, which was just a small creek running next to our campsite at that point. We’d spent some time getting everything set up, but decided to take a play break. The kids and the dogs were antsy, and eager to have some fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smaller Infinity Domain</title>
      <link>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/smaller-infinity-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 15:42:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/smaller-infinity-domain/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to smallerinfinity.com!
I have owned this domain for close to a decade now, and I have never made the time to make it anything more than a joke. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of how the domain looked yesterday to an external observer:
  Clearly, something more professional was warranted.
How I set this site up I got the inspiration for doing this site from this very excited post describing the ease of setting up a static site on github pages using GoHugo and Github Pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 07:18:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smallerinfinity.com/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Wow. Starting this with something named &amp;ldquo;First Post&amp;rdquo; inspires my &amp;ldquo;paralysis by analysis&amp;rdquo; response in a big way. For example, I just spent thirty seconds thinking about whether to change &amp;ldquo;inspires my&amp;rdquo; above to something else.
My name Seth McCarthy. I currently manage a software development team at BIOVIA, a brand of Dassault Systemes. For a long time I haven&amp;rsquo;t done anything technical outside of my job. It hasn&amp;rsquo;t been for lack of interest, just for lack of white-space in my schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>